

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

- Name
  Mateusz Makowski
- Address
  Szczecin
- Phone number +48883474273
- Email mateusz.makowski.102@gmail.com
- Date of birth 04/04/1995
- iii GenderMale➡ Driving licence
- B

  Mationality
- PL PL
- https://www.linkedin.com/in /mateusz-makowski-650155196/

#### **SKILLS**

CSS

SCSS Cypress

ECMAScript

Git

jQuery

**JavaScript** 

Next.js

Redux

React

**Tailwind** 

## **HOBBY**

- Metalcore
- Sourdough baking
- Fermentation of vegetables and fruits.
- Guitar playing
- Video games

# MATEUSZ MAKOWSKI

A passionate frontend developer with over 4 years of experience prioritizing continuous growth. Through interactions with clients from e-commerce and gambling industries, I am able to tailor individual approaches to clients and projects, ensuring their unique needs are met.



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jul 2019 - Aug 2019

#### Frontend developer

Squiz, Szczecin

- Creation of a single-page application according to Adobe XD mockups.
- Mainly utilized technologies: HTML, CSS.

Mar 2020 - Jun 2021

#### Junior Web Developer

IAI, Szczecin

- · Handling clients from the e-commerce industry.
- Developing online store projects using Adobe XD, as well as providing ongoing service, updates, and development.
- Utilized technologies: CSS (SCSS), ECMAScript 6, HTML, XML.

Jul 2021 - Present

#### Frontend Developer

SBBETTING SOFTWARE, Szczecin

- Solutions tailored for clients in the gambling industry, catering to major players from Poland and Africa.
- · Customer communication
- · Introduction of testing using Cypress technology.
- Introduction of account registration capabilities utilizing banking systems (myID)
- Utilized technologies: Styled components/Tailwind, HTML, CSS, ECMASCRIPT6+, REDUX, REACT, NEXT.JS, FRAMER-MOTION



# **EDUCATION**

o Oct 2015 - Jul 2018

# Bachelor's degree

University of Szczecin, Szczecin, Szczecin

- Completed degree: Cognitive Communication Studies
- Mainstream of studies: Philosophy, Web Development, Information Architecture